Guide to the Northup & O'Brien Architectural Records
Northup & O'Brien Architectural Records
- Financial Material, 1917-1956; 1917 1956; 3 linear feet
  - Account Book, 1926-1927 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Account Book, 1925-1926 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Account Book, 1927-1929 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Account Book, 1928-1929 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Account Book, 1929-1935 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Account Book, 1930-1935 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Account Book, 1935-1938 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Account Book, 1935-1939 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Account Book, 1940-1946 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Account Book, 1947-1948 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Estimate Book, May 1933- September 1934 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Estimate Book, September-November 1934 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Estimate Book, November 1934-July 1935 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Estimate Book, July-November 1935 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Estimate Book, November 1935-May 1936 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Estimate Book, May-November 1936 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Estimate Book, November 1936-April 1937 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Estimate Book, April-August 1937 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Estimate Book, August 1937-April 1938 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Estimate Book, April-September 1938 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Estimate Book, September-December 1938 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Estimate Book, January-April 1939 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Estimate Book, April-June 1939 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Estimate Book, June 1939-July 1940 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Estimate Book, June-December 1940 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Estimate Book, June 1940 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Estimate Book, July 1940-April 1941 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Estimate Book, April 1941-February 1942 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Estimate Book, March 1946-May 1947 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Estimate Book, May-September 1947 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Estimate Book, September 1947-May 1948 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Estimate Book, May 1948 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Estimate Book, September-November 1950 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Estimate Book, undated (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Account Book, 1938-1942 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Material, 1935-1948, undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Personnel Ledger, 1950 (Box 69)
  - Personnel Ledger, 1951 (Box 69)
  - Personnel Ledger, 1952 (Box 69)
  - Personnel Ledger, 1953 (Box 69)
  - Personnel Ledger, 1954 (Box 69)
  - Personnel Ledger, 1955 (Box 69)
  - Personnel Ledger, Pt. 1, 1956 (Box 69)
  - Personnel Ledger, Pt. 2, 1956 (Box 69)